Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Additional Photographs 5917 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Textile Assn. (Signing) 5/4/1972 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  was b23f62 -- 18 photographs
- Theater Development Fund (Box 42, Folder 32)
  was b23f63 -- 3 photographs
- Jim Thorpe Outing - Aug. 23, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  was b23f64 -- 6 photographs
- Jim Thorpe, PA -- 6/2/1985 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  was b23f65 -- 2 photographs
- Larry Thorpe (Box 42, Folder 35)
  was b23f66 -- 7 photographs
- Lombardo Toledano at IFLWU Convention (Box 42, Folder 36)
  was b23f67 - 1 photograph
- Rep. Toricelli Fund-Raiser & Donation, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  was b23f68 -- 5 photographs
- Charles Tournas & Nick Rassias, Lynn Mass. Stoppage 11/15 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  was b23f69 -- 1 photograph
- Trade Delegation to Wash. 2/4/1981 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  was b23f70 -- 5 photographs
- Trustees - All Funds (Box 42, Folder 40)
  was b23f71 - 10 photographs
- Trustees Meeting - 12/1974 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  was b23f72
- FLM Trustees Meeting -- Nov. 17, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  was b23f73 -- 1 photograph
- Trustees Meeting - 6/17/1976 (Box 42, Folder 43)
  was b23f74 -- 2 photographs
- Trustees Meeting - Arrowwood - May 4-6, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 44)
  was b23f75 -- 10 photographs
- Trustees Meeting - Dec. 14, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  was b23f76 -- 3 photographs
- Unemployed Aid Committee (Box 42, Folder 46)
  was b23f77 - 1 photograph
- Union Holiday Party - Dec. 1985 (Box 42, Folder 47)
  was b23f78 - 25 photographs
- Union Label Show - June 1969 (Box 42, Folder 48)
  was b23f79 -- 9 photographs
- Union Outing - Aug. 29, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 49)
  was b23f80 -- 7 photographs
- UFCW Convention - 6/1979 (Box 42, Folder 50)
  was b23f81 - 9 photographs
- UFCW Women's Affairs, Civil Rights, Political Action Cong. Wash. DC 8/25-26-27/1980 (Box 42, Folder 51)
  was b23f82 -- 8 photographs
- UFCW Convention - Aug. 1-5, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 52)
  was b23f83 -- 11 photographs
- United Fur Cuttings Meeting -- April 17, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 53)
  was b23f84 -- 2 photographs
- United Fur Cuttings Party - Dec. 1968 (Box 42, Folder 54)
  was b23f85 -- 3 photographs
- United Mechanics 150 Meeting - 5/3/1973 (Box 42, Folder 55)
  was b23f86 -- 1 photograph
- United mechanics 150 Meeting -- 3/20/1975 (Box 42, Folder 56)
  was b23f87 -- 2 photographs
- United Mechanics 150 Membership meeting - 10/1975 (Box 42, Folder 57)
  was b23f88 - 2 photographs
- United Mechanics 150 Meeting - 10/28/1976 (Box 42, Folder 58)
  was b23f89 -- 3 photographs
- United Mechanics 150 Division Meeting - 4/1978 (Box 42, Folder 59)
  was b23f90 -- 4 photographs
- United Mechanics 150 Meeting - 4/30/1981 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  was b23f91 -- 7 photographs
- U.S. Blindstitch Contract Negotiations - 3/1985 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  was b23f92 -- 3 photographs
- Unused Pictures - Dec.-Jan. 1985 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  was b2393 -- 3 photographs
- VALB Luncheon - April 28, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  was b23f94 -- 7 photographs
- Anthony Vassura (Box 43, Folder 5)
  was b2395 -- 1 photograph
- Veterans Dance (Box 43, Folder 6)
  was b2396 - 3 photographs
- Victory Meeting Picture - Cover - Fur and Leather Worker (Box 43, Folder 7)
  was b2397 - 1 photograph
- Vietnam Moratorium Rally Oct. 15-1969 -- Tempo Dec '69 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  was b2398 -- 9 photographs
- Voice of the Immigrant Henry Robinson - 4/1978 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  was b2399 - 3 photographs
- Voter Registration (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Vivian Wadlington Commencement - 6/28/1983 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Wage Freeze Rally - Oct 1971 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  was b23f102
- Ervin Wagner Testimonial - 1/15/1966 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  was b23f103 -- 26 photographs
- Ervin Wagner Testimonial 1/15/1966 (2) (Box 43, Folder 14)
  was b23f103 -- 21 photographs
- We Mourn Our Loss - Jan.-Feb. 1986 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  was b23f104 - 1 photograph
- Webster Soda Fountain - 2/13/1975 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  was b23f105 -- 3 photographs
- Sam Weinberg Retirement Party - 1/30/1981 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  was b23f106 - 8 photographs
- Welfare Booklet Pictures (Box 43, Folder 18)
  was b23f107 - 3 photographs
- Welfare Fund Trustees (Box 43, Folder 19)
  was b23f109 - 1 photograph
- Wellsboro - Allegheny Div. (Jt. Council 3) - April 23, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  was b23f109 - 3 photographs
- Wellsboro Ratification Meeting - April 1969 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  was b23f110 - 1 photograph
- Westfield Christmas Party 1967 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  was b23f111 - 15 photographs
- Westfield Tanning Contract Signing 4/1/1983 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  was b23f112 -- 1 photograph
- White Lake (Box 43, Folder 24)
  was b23f113 -- 4 photographs
- White Lake - Aerial Shots (Box 43, Folder 25)
  was b23f114 -- 3 photographs
- White Lake - Local 64 -- June 1954 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  was b23f115 -- 15 photographs
- White Lake Lodge (Box 43, Folder 27)
  was b23f116 -- 10 photographs
- White Lake Lodge, 1954 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  was b23f117 -- 26 photographs
- White Lake Outing (Box 43, Folder 29)
  was b23f118 -- 13 photographs
- White Lake Outing -- 9/1951 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  was b23f119 -- 7 photographs
- White Lake Outing - Sept. 1951 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  was b23f120 -- 19 photographs
- White Lake Outing - 9/1953 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  was b23f121 -- 19 photographs
- Wildlife Management Class at F.I.T. (Box 43, Folder 33)
  was b23f122 -- 5 photographs
- Wildlife Management Class FIT (Box 43, Folder 34)
  was b23f123 -- 2 photographs
- Wilmington Meeting -- 1/31/1979 (Box 43, Folder 35)
  was b23f124 -- 6 photographs
- Wilmington Chemical Exam -- 2/21/1982 (Box 43, Folder 36)
  was b23f125 -- 3 photographs
- Wilmington Chemical Shop Meeting -- 11/1982 (Box 43, Folder 37)
  was b23f126 -- 2 photographs
- Wilmington Chemical Negotiations - 3/1983 (Box 43, Folder 38)
  was b23f127 -- 4 photographs
- Wilmington Chemical Arbitration -- 6/1983 (Box 43, Folder 39)
  was b23f128 -- 2 photographs
- Wilmington Chemical Contract -- 4/1984 (Box 43, Folder 40)
  was b23f129 -- 2 photographs
- Women Strike for Peace - March 1970 (Box 43, Folder 41)
  was b23f130 -- 1 photograph
- Women's Luncheon - Convention (Box 43, Folder 42)
  was b23f131 -- 32 photographs
- Women's Trade Union Conference -- 1/19/1974 (Box 43, Folder 43)
  was b23f132 -- 1 photograph
- Workers Compensation Seminar -- Apr. 27, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 44)
  was b23f136 -- 4 photographs
- Woolis Testimonial Dinner -- June 17, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 45)
  was b23f133 -- 24 photographs
- Woolis Luncheon -- 4/3/1980 (Box 43, Folder 46)
  was b23f134
- Woolis Retirement Party -- 4/2/1982 (Box 43, Folder 47)
  was b23f135 -- 11 photographs
- Working conditions (Box 43, Folder 48)
  was b23f137 -- 2 photographs
- World Youth Festival Breakfast -- 5/9/1985 (Box 43, Folder 49)
  was b23f138 -- 2 photographs
- Yugoslav Delegation -- May 24, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 50)
  was b23f139 -- 5 photographs
- Sam Zelitan at Retirees Center (Box 43, Folder 51)
  was b23f140 -- 1 photograph
- Walt Zgleszewski (Box 43, Folder 52)
  was b23f141 -- 2 photographs; news paper
- Zola Zembe - Newark -- 10/1977 (Box 43, Folder 53)
  was b23f142 -- 6 photographs
- Zucker - United Fur Cutters Party (Box 43, Folder 54)
  was b23f143 -- 3 photographs
- Shop Ch Conference - 3/1968 (handwritten info. From back of photo) (Box 44, Folder 1)
  was b23f4 -- was found laying on top of folders in box 23, so moved for safety of photo -- [oversized photo]
- Contents from box 24 - Unlabeled (Box 44, Folder 2)
  was b24 -- 11 photographs
- Contents from box 25 - Unlabeled (Box 44, Folder 3)
  was b25 -- 17 photographs
- American Photograph Corporation Strike, AMC & BW; Local 251 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  was b26f1 -- 13 photographs
- Childrens' Christmas Parties (Box 45, Folder 2)
  was b26f2 -- 22 photographs --- see also b1, f134
- Conference/Conventions (Box 45, Folder 3)
  was b26f3 -- 9 photographs --- see also b18f54
- Executive Board - World War II Years - Negative (Box 45, Folder 4)
  was b26f4 --
- Ben Gold (Box 45, Folder 5)
  was b26f5 -- 3 photographs -- see also b5 f13
- Jewish Day Picket Line (Box 45, Folder 6)
  was b26f6 -- 3 photographs
- May Day (Box 45, Folder 7)
  was b26f7 -- 2 photographs -- see also b8, f40-46; b9, f1-5
- Parades (Box 45, Folder 8)
  was b26f8 -- 4 photographs -- see also b10, f10-12
- Potash, Irving (Box 45, Folder 9)
  was b26f9 -- 1 photograph -- see also b10, f41
- Cohey, Cecil Photos (Box 46, Folder 1)
  was b27f1 -- 4 photographs
- Detroit (Box 46, Folder 2)
  was b27f2 -- 1 photograph
- Executive Boards - International (Box 46, Folder 3)
  was b27f3 -- 3 photographs -- see also bx47f3
- Sports (Box 46, Folder 4)
  was b27f4 -- 1 photograph -- see also bx11f52; bx12f1-2
- Stevenson Market Rally - 1952 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  was b27f5 -- 5 photographs -- see also bx 12f6
- Conferences (Box 47, Folder 1)
  was b28f1 -- 13 photographs -- see also b26f16
- Conventions - Misc. (Box 47, Folder 2)
  was b28f2 -- 9 photographs -- see also bx 2f38; bx 25f16
- Dinners, Affairs, etc. (Box 47, Folder 3)
  was b28f3 -- 22 photographs -- see also bx 26, f3-8
- Executive Boards - International (Box 47, Folder 4)
  was b28f4 -- 3 photographs -- see also bx 46f2
- Anti-Apartheid March and Rally - 6/14/1986 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  was box 30 - renumbered in reorganization of collection -- see also bx1, f18
- Borden's negotiations - 1/2/1972 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  was box 30 - renumbered in reorganization of collection - see also bx 1, f48
- Greyhound Demonstration - 11/23/1983 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  was box 30 - renumbered in reorganization of collection -- see also bx 5, f20
- Henry, Lyndon (Box 48, Folder 4)
  was box 30 - renumbered in reorganization of collection -- see also bx 5, f34
- Immigration Demonstration (Box 48, Folder 5)
  was box 30 - renumbered in reorganization of collection -- see also bx 6, f13
- Jobs Rally in Washington (Coutlakis): 4/26/1975 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  was box 30 - renumbered in reorganization of collection -- see also bx, f25
- Joint Council Officers (Box 48, Folder 7)
  was box 30 - renumbered in reorganization of collection -- see also: Bx6, f46
- Norelli, Armando (Box 48, Folder 8)
  was box 30 - renumbered in reorganization of collection -- see also: bx10, f4
- Norelli, Armando (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Prince Industries - FLM at work (Box 48, Folder 10)
  was box 30 - renumbered in reorganization of collection -- see also bx10, f43
- N.G. Slater - FLM members at work (Box 48, Folder 11)
  was box 30 - renumbered in reorganization of collection -- see also bx 11, f44
- United Fur Cutters - members at Work (Box 48, Folder 12)
  was box 30 - renumbered in reorganization of collection -- see also: bx12, f34
- Tempo - 12/1980 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  was box 30 - renumbered in reorganization of collection -- see also: bx 15, f52-54
- Anti-Avon Protest Rally 3/1972 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  was box 31 - renumbered in reorganization of collection -- see also bx1, f16
- Hollander, A. and Son (Box 49, Folder 2)
  was box 31 - renumbered in reorganization of collection -- see also bx 5, f38-41
- Hollander, A. and Son (Box 49, Folder 3)
  was box 31 - renumbered in reorganization of collection -- see also bx5, f38-41
- I.J. Fox Strike (Box 49, Folder 4)
  was box 31 - renumbered in reorganization of collection -- see also: bx6, f11
- I.J. Fox Strike (Box 49, Folder 5)
  was box 31 - renumbered in reorganization of collection -- see also: box6, ff11
- I.J. Fox Strike (Box 49, Folder 6)
- I.J. Fox Strike (Box 49, Folder 7)
  was box 31 - renumbered in reorganization of collection -- see also: Bx6, ff11
- Joint council Officers' (Box 49, Folder 8)
  was box 31 - renumbered in reorganization of collection -- see also bx6, f42-46
- Railex Strike - 7/1966 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  was box 31 - renumbered in reorganization of collection -- see also bx 11, f1
- Stofsky, George (Box 49, Folder 10)
  was box 31 - renumbered in reorganization of collection -- see also bx31, f10
- Strikes & Pickets (Box 49, Folder 11)
  was box 31 - renumbered in reorganization of collection -- see also: bx 12, f17
- Tempo: 10/1969 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  was box 31 - renumbered in reorganization of collection -- see also: bx14, f26-27
- Tempo - 6/1972 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  was box 31 - renumbered in reorganization of collection -- see also: bx 14, f 56-58
- Contents of box 32 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  was box 32 -- 17 oversize photographs
- Tempo - 3/1984 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  Was box 16, ff1 -- 17 Photographs
- Tempo 3/1984 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  Was box 16, ff2 - 18 photographs
- Tempo 6/1984 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  Was box 16, ff3 - 20 photographs
- Tempo 6/1984 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  Was box 16, ff4 - 15 photographs
- Tempo 6/1984 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  Was box 16, ff 5 19 photographs
- Tempo 10/1984, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  Was box 16, ff 6 16 photographs
- Tempo 10/1984 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  Was box 16, ff 7 20 photographs
- Tempo 12/1984-1/1985 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  Was box 16, ff 8 21 photographs
- Tempo - 12/1984-1/1985 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  Was box 16, ff 9 19 photographs
- Tempo 4/1985 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  Was box 16, ff 10 16 photographs
- Tempo 4/1985 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  Was box 16, ff 11 14 photographs
- Tempo 6/1985 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  Was box 16, ff 12 -- 21 photographs
- Tempo 6/1985 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  Was box 16, ff13 18 photographs
- Tempo 6/1985 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  Was box 16, ff14 14 photographs
- Tempo 6/1985 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  Was box 16, ff 15 14 photographs
- Tempo October 1985 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  Was box 16, ff16 23 photographs
- Tempo October 1985 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  Was box 16, ff 17 18 photographs
- Tempo #1 October 1985 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  Was box 16, ff 18 15 photographs
- Fifteenth Biennial Convention of the International Fur and Leather Workers Union of United States and Canada, CIO, May 20th, 1944, Atlantic City, NJ (Box 52, Folder 1)
  Panoramic box 29 found in Oversize area, not recorded in system -- Conventions - Misc. (see also Bx 2, ff 38; Bx 18, ff 54; Bx 28, ff 2)
- 16th Biennial Convention, International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada - CIO, May-1946, President Hotel, Atlantic City, NJ (Box 52, Folder 2)
- 13th Biennial Convention, International Fur Workers' Union of the United States and Canada - CIO Hotel President - Atlantic City - May 1939 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- 13th Biennial Convention, International Fur Workers' Union of the United States and Canada - CIO, Hotel President - Atlantic City, NJ - May 1939 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- 17th Biennial Convention, International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada, CIO - Steel Pier, Atlantic City, NJ, May 16-22, 1948 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- 17th Biennial Convention, International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada, CIO, Steel Pier, Atlantic City, NJ, May 16-22, 1948 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Fifteenth biennial Convention of the International Fur and Leather Workers Union of United States and Canada, CIO, May 20th, 1944, Atlantic City, NJ (Box 52, Folder 7)